GARY MARTIN

OBJECTIVE

Seeking to join the company to leverage my knowledge in building web and software applications . Looking to work with databases and different programming languages to achieve the desired result for my work assignments.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Cleanroom experience

Experience working with multiple chemicals.

Experience working with different tools and equipment to produce quality semiconductor wafers.

Proficient knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 5, JavaScript and DOM manipulation

Proficient in PHP and mySQL

Experience creating databases

Proficient in Figma and Photoshop

Knows how to optimize websites as well as make them accessible.

Understanding of SEO and best practices

Some UX Design and Research experience dealing with creating deliverables, gathering user data, creating wireframes, and the deconstruction of websites.

Quick learner who can adapt to certain changes and obstacles quickly.

People person who can empathize and figure out other people's problems.

EXPERIENCE

MACOM TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS

JULY 2022-PRESENT

Currently work as a semiconductor technician in a cleanroom setting to produce quality wafers using multiple chemicals as well as multiple different tools and equipment.

WEBASTO ROOF SYSTEMS

April 2021-August 2021

Worked as a Machine Operator. Had to quickly learn how to operate the machine to keep up with the high demand. Attention to detail was needed to make sure the parts were properly put on the machine.

MWT WIRELESS

August 2020-April 2021

Worked as a Retail Sales Consultant. Main duties were to sale ATT products and services to consumers. Had to adapt quickly to different types of consumers and listen closely to their problem and come up with a solution that would best suit their needs.

ELC CONSULTANTS

December 2018-July 2020

Worked as a Cell Phone Repair Technician. Main duties were to repair and audit cell phones and other electronic devices. Also aided in the shipping and sales department taking orders and talking to customers via email when needed.

CERTIFICATIONS

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATION GIVEN BY WASHTENAW COMMUNITY COLLEGE

EDUCATION

AAS IN SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT. PURSUING BS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE.

My studies consist of the development side which is coding static webpages using HTML and CSS and dynamic websites JavaScript and their frameworks.

The design side focuses more on UI/UX Design. My focus in design is currently more on the UX Design and Research side. I have created personas based on certain users of a webpage as well as deliverables dealing with a competitive analysis of different companies, gathering user data to conduct card sorts, and deconstructing the structures of websites. I have also prepared wireframes and done interface redesigns for websites using Figma.

Having a background in studying computer science can help aid in understanding and implementing data structures and algorithms. I am also able to understand the theoretical aspects of programming such as call stacks and trees.

REFERENCES

SEAN HAGER, AREA MANAGER AT MWT WIRELESS

Phone Number: (734)-864-2675

TANIECE BRADLEY, STORE MANAGER AT MWT WIRELESS

Phone Number: (810)-288-3147

JAMES EWING, RETAIL SALES CONSULTANT AT MWT WIRELESS

Phone Number: (313)-888-0631

WILL SNIPES, SHIFT SUPERVISOR AT WEBASTO ROOF SYSTEMS

Phone Number: (313)-932-8884

DAN GRAUWICKEL, COMPANY OWNER AT ELC CONSULTANTS

Phone Number: (734)-476-4916